yeah over 200 shows and no irish people
like i can't tell why maybe just
irish people like a dry bar no no no no
and in a dry bar and i can't say any bad
words
oh no no no no
i've been acclimatizing well i'm four
buckets of popcorn deep so anything
could happen
ah it's great being an immigrant here in
your fine country though it's
really quite a contrast to ireland like
when i grew up we had pretty much
zero percent immigration i was the
brownest person for miles
just just a hint of a ten they were like
look at him
suspicious
and now we have 17 immigration and we
are the only country in the whole world
that doesn't have a single political
party in parliament opposing immigration
the only one and we can't because we
have shagged our way
into all your family trees
[Applause]
many of you don't even know it
that day you get your 23 and me results
you're just like dude dude you're not
going to believe this yeah i'm like 17
irish this whole time i thought it was a
filipino
and then they're like well that explains
the drinking
because you do i i didn't notice that
when americans mess up drinking they
blame
my people i don't know if you've heard
this to be like
oh my gosh i got so wasted on friday
night i don't remember a thing
must be my irish jeans
so i looked it up and it turns out the
tree top selling beers in america are
budweiser
bud light and for variety coors light
that's
that's not an irish jeans issue that's a
credit score issue
[Laughter]
[Applause]
we we really do shag our way in
everywhere like if they make black
panther too they'll be an irish guy in
wakandan
we turn up everywhere and that was a
real pivotal moment for america it
wasn't it was about time like
14.6 of americans are african-american
that was your biggest minority group
that movie black panther
getting a superhero i thought that was
amazing who is the next
biggest minority group in america to get
a superhero and i looked it up and it
turns out 11.6
of americans think they're irish
that's 25 million people we only have 5
million people in ireland
and we are not ready for a superhero
what would an irish superhero do you're
like look at him he just got drunk and
successfully drove home there he goes
there
he's a superhero why didn't he fly and
you're like oh no mostly filipino
couldn't handle the
oh my drink that was so funny oh
oh for more check out check out the
drywall app
[Music]